

Muhammad Radifa

Junior Web Developer

madifa.my.id MuhammadRadifa in linkedin.com/in/radifa/

I am an Informatics Engineering student, I have a strong understanding of programming languages and web development and have experience in software development projects. I have an interest and deepening my knowledge in the field of web development

Education

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering (2021 - present) GPA 3.76 Sekolah Tinggi Manajemen Informatika dan Komputer Widya Cipta Dharma

Experience

Labcom Wicida

Lab Assistant (May 2023 - Present)

support the operation and success of practicum activities and setting up the necessary equipment and software, ensuring laboratory safety and order, and providing assistance to students during practical sessions.

Wicida Developers Community

Lead (2022 - *Present*)

As a Leader in a developer community coordinate collaboration between team members and create and facilitate discussion spaces for students. These responsibilities include organizing and managing discussion forums that allow students to discuss the latest technological developments.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika

Head of Research And Development Division (2022 - Present)

As Head of the Research and Development Division whose task is to accommodate STMIK Widya Cipta Dharma Information Engineering students in terms of research and development in the field of technology.

Staff Research And Development (2021 - 2022)

Assisting in Work Program Activities in the Science and Technology and R&D Division, namely assisting in National Edutek Webinar activities which were attended by hundreds of participants

Certificate & Achievement

- 3rd UNM Digital Fest Web Development Competition
- Finalist Lo Kreatif Web & Mobile Development Competition
- Junior Web Developer (badan nasional sertifikasi profesi)
- React Web Developer (Dicoding)
- laravel web development (sanbercode)
- golang backend development (sanbercode)